<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>zzdjk6's blog</title><link href="http://zzdjk6.github.io/myblog/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://zzdjk6.github.io/myblog/feeds/android.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://zzdjk6.github.io/myblog/</id><updated>2014-09-11T18:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Find Android Keystore And Password Back</title><link href="http://zzdjk6.github.io/myblog/find-android-keystore-and-password-back.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-09-11T18:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>zzdjk6 (Shenghan Chen)</name></author><id>tag:zzdjk6.github.io,2014-09-11:myblog/find-android-keystore-and-password-back.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I lost an android keystore file but I need it to publish app update to google play store. (I replaced it with new one carelessly.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I found I'm not the only one have this issue, most of people say you can do nothing, but I found it back successfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;use Data Rescue to find the key store file back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;generate some keystore files and use "FileIQ" function of this software to train it recognize keystore file type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;change search engine preference to set the limit size of keystore file, I use 100KB, maybe 1000KB is better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;disable other file type recognition to speed up reconstruction phase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;start a deep scan and wait for hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you will find some files in "User Defined" nodes, recover them all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;use &lt;a href="https://code.google.com/p/android-keystore-password-recover/"&gt;Android Keystore Password Recovery&lt;/a&gt; to check these file one by one, see if it is the one you need. (you don't have to know the password of these key store, just use a dict.txt and "-m 2" to see the key alias and create date of the keystore file, this tool can show these basic information even the password is wrong.)
If you're lucky like me, you find your keystore file back now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you forgot your password, you have to go further, continue use &lt;a href="https://code.google.com/p/android-keystore-password-recover/"&gt;Android Keystore Password Recovery&lt;/a&gt; or other tools to find your password back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>