<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title><![CDATA[zzdjk6&#039;s Blog]]></title>
    <link href="http://zzdjk6.github.io/Blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="http://zzdjk6.github.io/Blog/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-01T00:12:54+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://zzdjk6.github.io/Blog/</id>
        <generator uri="http://sculpin.io/">Sculpin</generator>
            <entry>
            <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Choose Sculpin As Blog Engine!]]></title>
            <link href="http://zzdjk6.github.io/Blog/blog/2014/08/31/i-choose-sculpin-as-blog-engine"/>
            <updated>2014-08-31T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
            <id>http://zzdjk6.github.io/Blog/blog/2014/08/31/i-choose-sculpin-as-blog-engine</id>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After some tries, I finally choose <a href="http://sculpin.io/">Sculpin</a> as my blog engine.</p>

<p>As you know, a lot of programmer may go through these events:</p>

<ol>
<li>sign up on a common blog site and write</li>
<li>then set up a standalone blog with dedicated domain (e.g use wordpress)</li>
<li>finally find a static site generator (e.g jekyll) and put the blog on Github Pages or sth like that.</li>
</ol>

<p>I have a quickview of some static site generators, include Ruby-based (jekyll),
Javascript-based (Hexo), Python-based (Pelican), Java-based (jBake) then finally PHP-based (Sculpin).</p>

<p>I was a contract web developer with PHP as main weapon.
Before that I wrote some Python, ASP.net, and some Core java.</p>

<p>Ruby-based, Python-based and Javascript-based solutions got a large user base,
but I find these solutions not fit me, because:</p>

<ul>
<li>It seems has all features I need.(jBake sucks, sorry :)</li>
<li>It seems easier to cusomize since I feel more confident when using a tool written in a language I'm most skillfull.</li>
<li>Recently I find myself don't like these dynamic-typed language without explict type hint any more (e.g Ruby,Python,Js).</li>
<li>I find only PHP-based solutions all target at the same template engine in common - Twig,
it's de facto standard in Symfony-based community. Template engine of other language based solution vary
from each other. Too many choices drives me crazy.</li>
</ul>

<p>If you have the similar problem with me, give <a href="http://sculpin.io/">Sculpin</a> a try.</p>
]]></content>
        </entry>
    </feed>